PHU QUANG

JUNIOR FRONTEND



EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT-BRANCH IN HO CHI MINH CITY

08/2017 - 07/2021

Specialized: Information technology

Graduated

EXPERIENCE

THE JIZAKA CO., LTD

11/2021 - 08/2022

dev frontend

- Build website interface from files PSD.
- Using framework laravel, javascript, php, bootstrap, material...
- I have learned a lot from the projects I have done.
- Undertake small projects based on design files. (react)

THE EBOOKING CO., LTD

08/2022 - 10/2022

dev frontend

- Build website interface from files PSD.
- Using framework React, Redux, Ant Design

HDBANK

12/2022 - Present

dev frontend

- -Core-Banking.
- Build website interface from files PSD.
- Using Oracle-form, Sql, PLSQL.

PROJECT

https://www.hana-tochi-to.jp/

http://app.dev.ebk.vn/

https://thuongmaidientu-2022.herokuapp.com/

- **1** 01/01/1998
- Nam
- **** 0382520045
- daiphu094@gmail.com
- → HCMC
- i https://www.facebook.com/profile.php? id=100023609266065

SUMMARY

I graduated as an IT engineer and have 1 experience in Web Development, I learned a lot during the project. I look forward to challenging myself to develop and improve my programming skills. My biggest goal is to use my technical abilities to bring many common benefits to individuals and organizations.

SKILLS

Skills

- -Javascript/Typescript , html , CSS, SCSS ,Jquery.
- Bootstrap, tailwind, Antd,
- Reactis, redux, Nextis, Firebase
- RestAPI, Git, mongoDB, mysql, Oracle,
 Scrum, mongoDB, postman,
- -Photoshop, Ai , Figma.
- -English (At the level of reading understanding and a little bit of listening.
- -Team Working.

□ CAREER GOALS

- Short-term: Have a stable job Become an excellent employee, add accumulatively lots of experience, practice handling skills Efficient, accurate, fast work.
- Long-term: There are opportunities for promotion.

CO HOBBIES

Chess

Badminton